Hi, in this segment we're going to talk about a bash.
And, the way I do bashes is because I'm right handed, I use the counterclockwise spin to do a bash.
Now, a bash is different than a brush because you're actually hitting it a lot harder, and a bash is really intended to put to a lot more spin on the Frisbee.
So, if the Frisbee is going counterclockwise position, and it's here, you strike it right on the side. So you're basically coming on, you're going to cup your hand a little bit.
A lot of people think you're hitting it from this side, but you're not.
You're actually hitting it from the far side, hitting it on the edge and really trying to put more spin on it.
So there's the counter spin, the set up, the bash, the set, the bash, the tip, bash, bash, and it increases the spin.
Again, you want to hit it with the palm.
The meaty part.
The fat part of your hand so it doesn't hurt.
If you go and hit it with your fingers, it's going to give you a little bit of pain, and it won't put as much spin on it.
So here, around the outside, and really try to crank that spin up.
One more time.
Here, bash.